{"data":[{"question":"What the spokesman had said in the news ___not exactly right.","a":"is proved","b":"proves","c":"was","d":"proved","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: action \"prove\" happened after action \"say\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"We are sad to hear that our team ___theirs in the match yesterday.","a":"was won","b":"was defeated","c":"was beaten","d":"was struck","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Strike: to deliberately hit someone or something with your hand or a weapon","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Sandra can hardly ___ the difference between these two phrases.","a":"speak","b":"point","c":"tell","d":"talk","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tell:to know something or be able to recognize something because of certain signs that show this","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"When Yvonne phoned Irene, Irene could not hear clearly what she was ___.","a":"talking","b":"speaking","c":"telling","d":"saying","answer":"4","explain":"\n-You use say when you are mentioning someone's exact words\n-You tell\t a story, a joke, a lie, or the truth\n- When one person is saying things, you can use talkor speak, but talk is more usual and speak slightly literary\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"I am sorry. I've ___ your DVD at home again. I'll bring it tomorrow.","a":"laid","b":"forgotten","c":"left","d":"put","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Leave: to make or allow something or someone to stay in a place when you go away","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"That boy studies hard. I ___ him to do well on the exam.","a":"expect","b":"like","c":"need","d":"think","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Expect:  to think that something will happen because it seems likely or has been planned","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Joshua ___ studying the Chinese geography ten years ago.","a":"set out","b":"set about","c":"set down","d":"set up","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Set about: to start doing or dealing with something, especially something that needs a lot of time and effort","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher told the class to ___ their books.","a":"put by","b":"put away","c":"put up","d":"put on","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Put away: to put something in the place where it is usually kept","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Your grandma looks ill. You'd better ___ a doctor.","a":"call","b":"call on","c":"call at","d":"call for","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Call: to telephone someone\n- Call on= visit\n- Call for: if a group of people calls for something, they ask publicly for something to be done\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"},{"question":"Sean was working at his desk last night when the lamp suddenly went ___.","a":"away","b":"off","c":"over","d":"out","answer":"4","explain":"\n - Go out: to stop burning or shining","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"19","type":"1"}]}